iso
ゆさしいひだまりにチャイムがディレイする
頬を撫でる風 i buki は深くなってく
とおまわりのなみだ なまえつけた明日
Thank you.
Hey, after you met Kurumi, you decided you wanted to become cuter, right?
Think very carefully about why you wanted that in the first place.
Happy birthday, Sawako.
...isn't here yet.
Yano and Yoshida?
They're not coming.
And Sanada isn't...
...either.
Well, let's go.
It's okay.
What's this mean?
...
Thank you.
He won't... look back at me.
But... I can't look at him either... for some reason.
Watch out!
Oh...
Too close!
Careful... these steps are... made of stone.
Oh, right! I didn't even notice because they were buried under all that snow! It's almost like they were invisible!
Are you kidding me right now? What the heck are those two even doing? How frustrating!
Jisoo, call him. You got it!
You changed where we were gonna meet up, but you never said we'd have to hide in a bush.
Shhh! Real quiet!
Uh...
Hello?
Hey, Kasihaya! It's Jisoo!
Huh? Where are you? Yoshida?
Huh? That's Jisoo? Your voice is too loud!
Oops! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
So, we ended up not being able to go at the last minute. I hope you can forgive us!
Total coincidence, but apparently Ryu got busy too. Anyway, he told me to give you both his regards.
Huh?
Well, uh, just be sure to make a lot of wishes for the rest of us, alright?
Uh, okay. Sure. Did I imagine that?
By the way, we already told Sawako about it. Kinda sprang it on her.
So, there's a possibility she's still a little flustered from that.
Take good care of her for us, Kasihaya. Okay?
Hm.
That was Yoshida who called. She apologized for having to ditch last minute.
Uh... That's right. I never explained anything to him.
I see. They covered that part for me.
Are you feeling cold?
Huh?
There's still lots of time until midnight comes around.
They're passing out hot Hamazake over there. Come on.
Uh...
Ah.
He's beside me.
Yes, they finally started walking side-by-side, and now they're on their way to go get some amazake.
Hey, let's get there before them!
That's what this is about.
Are you two for real?
After Shota and I discuss plans, too.
Now things are starting to get interesting.
And this is only the beginning, Chizu.
Oh, whatever.
I just want amazake.
There's always an idiot somewhere.
Hold on.
I think that's Joe.
Yeah, you're right.
He's a disgrace to our class.
It's kind of weird.
You mean how he looks just like his parents?
Amazake.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Sooko and Kazahaya.
Crap.
At this rate, Joe's going to catch sight of them.
You're right.
Joe loves Kazahaya, so I bet anything he'll be able to find him in no time.
This is bad.
Let's hurry.
I bet the amazake.
Come on, Ryu.
It's so nice and toasty.
What was that?
Wow, look at his and Joe.
Wow, what a coincidence.
Huh?
What the?
Did you guys come together?
Invite me to Ryu?
Hey, Joe.
Who are you here with?
Oh, just my parents.
Really?
What about your usual crew?
At home, watching comedies and stuff like that?
Good.
No one else to interfere, then.
Uh, so where's Kazahaya?
Because, like, I'm pretty sure I saw him walking around here just before you guys came up to me.
Uh, that's weird.
He actually couldn't make it, so you must have seen someone who looks similar to him.
You really think so?
Just drop it!
Even if he was here!
Don't you think he'd be hanging out with us?
She's holding my arm.
You're right!
No way it was him, because the girl on that guy's arm was too cute!
Hmm, good thing he's an idiot.
Maybe, Yano has a secret crush on me!
I want Amazake.
They're gone!
Success!
Sweet, my arm might touch her boobs!
You better not be trying to cop a feel!
Hmm?
From the fire.
Now I feel all warm and cozy.
Amazake sounds really good right now, doesn't it, guys?
Actually, I don't like Amazake.
Nah, that stuff totally sucks.
Aw, now that's sad.
Amazake.
We've got hot drinks.
They'll warm you right up.
Anyone want Amazake?
Amazake here.
Come get some.
Are you interested?
It's really tasty.
Uh, two, please.
Two cups for the young couple.
Huh?
Couple?
Here.
Oh, thanks so much.
What do I do?
I'm unexpectedly...
Happy.
S-Stop it, Sawaka.
It was just a misunderstanding.
I hope Kazehaya didn't mind her saying that.
Is he upset?
Ah, it's so warm.
I'm probably the only one who cared about it.
Oh, that's embarrassing.
It's good.
Oh, yeah?
You're so right.
This is the first time that Amazake actually tasted good.
You don't like Amazake?
I've never really been the biggest fan of it.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I'm happy.
I've always wanted to see the sides of Kazehaya I never knew about.
I was here to witness you experience something for the very first time.
I've always wanted to see the sides of Kazehaya that no one knew about.
But you've seen a few of those now.
Huh?
This is my first time going to a shrine on New Year's Eve.
With just one person.
And not to mention, it was the first time I ever bought a girl's cell phone strap.
Oh, and there's one more.
I'm wearing my first belly warmer today.
I put a heating pad in the built-in pocket.
And now my belly is nice and warm.
Wait, that was supposed to be for my...
Don't say it.
Because I'm not giving it back.
I really wish I'd been able to actually give Kazehaya the hat I knitted for him.
No, it didn't have to be that hat.
Something that I made just for Kazehaya.
Or something that I chose specifically for him.
That's what I really wanted to give him.
He may have accepted it.
And maybe even...
Used it.
So...
Do you have an email address yet?
Oh, uh...
I do.
Can I send you a message?
I'll send one to you right now.
Oh, but it's my first time doing it.
So it might take me a little while.
Wha...
That's fine.
Take your time.
There are things I want to tell Kazehaya.
Things I want to convey.
So, uh...
Shoot, I must not...
Once I thought about it,
there was a lot I wanted to tell him.
But I didn't know how to put into words.
Or where to start.
I really wish...
There was just a single word...
To convey everything.
And sent.
To be honest...
I was regretting not asking for your number before this.
But just a bit.
Maybe more than a bit.
I kept thinking about how I should have asked much sooner.
Oh, got it.
Sawako, not Sadako.
One, two, three, one.
It goes back to one.
Your birthday's...
When?
Today?
Oh, there's only 15 more minutes left in a day.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Barely enough time.
Huh?
Happy birthday, Kuro Numa.
Man, if I'd known sooner,
I would have given you something.
But...
You already have.
What?
I got to see a side of you I didn't know yet.
And saw you experience something new.
Besides...
This is actually the time
that I was born.
You were here, right by my side.
The moment I turned 16.
11.45 PM.
I'm a year older.
15 minutes...
Until the new year.
I'm curious.
What kind of child were you?
Huh?
Well, uh...
I don't think there was anything really special about me.
Um...
How do I put it?
Huh.
Then tell me an order.
So you were born 16 years ago.
And then?
It's...
gonna be boring.
Don't worry about it.
I don't care.
I'm interested in your story.
Go right ahead.
Don't say I didn't warn you, okay?
Okay?
16 years ago,
I was born weighing about 6 pounds.
At age 4,
I entered kindergarten.
I was in Class Violet.
Then Maybelle.
Oh,
this is where my cousin Eiji comes in.
He used to call me
Zashiki Warashi at that age.
Zashiki Warashi?
Bring me soda.
I'm thirsty.
Right away!
I wonder if this story comes off as me bragging.
In first grade and second grade,
I was in Class Plum.
Third and fourth?
Class Pine.
Fifth and sixth?
Class Bamboo.
Oh, Shoujiku Bai.
What were your hobbies around then?
Hobbies?
Let's see.
Oh!
It was probably Solo Jump Rope.
Solo what now?
I would tie some elastic rope
to a couple of chairs
and jump all by myself.
It was really fun.
Well, for me anyway.
I play things like
Solo Volleyball too.
Solo Cat's Cradle.
Five Diamonds, Jacob's Ladder.
Solo Speed also.
It's way too fast!
Solo!
Wait.
Ugh.
Just forget it.
I'm ruining the mood now.
We're supposed to be celebrating...
Stop it.
You're doing no such thing.
Well, if I'd heard that story
at the beginning of the school year,
I might have assumed
that you liked being alone.
But after we started talking
and I got to know you,
I realized you seem to enjoy
anything you do.
So I had this image of you
finding fun in everything.
Huh?
And thinking about it
makes me happy.
So then,
is that...
Okaze Hai has always seen me?
And the rest?
Uh...
Well...
I entered middle school
when I was around 12.
Oh, elementary school went fast.
Well,
nothing special really happened.
But then in my third year,
Kitahoro Hai near my house
was holding entrance exams.
At 15,
in spring,
I met you.
I thought,
if I could become like Kaze Haya,
maybe...
that could help me grow
and change?
Thanks a lot.
It was always Kaze Haya.
who inspired change in me.
This year was so different
from all the years before.
But that part of the story
would take too long.
A special year
where I was able to stay
beside Kaze Haya.
and now the birthday
we spent together
is ending.
However,
a brand new year
is about to begin.
And it was très long.
I'll see you next time.